Thank you for watching.
I started a new one, so it's not the one you just saw.
He is not here.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for your time.
We are Ukka.
We are Sanseiju.
We are Seizermacher.
We are Gunther.
We are Mimino
We are Rina Murachi
I am Idris.
I'm sorry to bother you.
So, there was a little bit of a problem once.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Today, we're going to look back on our spring tour
So today, we're going to do a little recap of the spring tour.
I'm going to take a look back today.
I'd like to take a look back today.
Yes, sir.
It's been quite a long time.
It's cold, but we waited a long time.
They cooked a variety of dishes. They look delicious.
Bon appétit. Let's eat first.
Please put your hands together.
Bon appétit!
Everyone, to the sea.
Catch, catch, catch!
Under the sea
Time on the sea on the sea on the sea
Yes, sir.
Thanks and if you like this video, please like, subscribe to the channel, comment and subscribe to the channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye.
Thank you for watching.
No microphone. Cell phone.
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's eat.
Yes, sir. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
Let's eat.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's okay. We'll just eat.
Yes, sir.
While you eat.
Let's go home.
Yes, ma'am.
So, this time...
This tour will be held on February 26th.
Finally...
I'll be speaking.
Please do.
So, this tour is going to be
February 26th.
This tour started on February 26th at Kamakura Hall.
This tour
I think it will be announced by the first of December
After that, I think...
I think it was after that.
Before that, at some other show...
That's a bra, isn't it?
That's right.
At some concert.
Oh...
Around here?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's when I started thinking about the list.
That's right.
I've been looking at it for quite a while.
Right.
And the truth is, we got the list because the staff decided to do it.
But there were some comments from the staff that they wanted to direct the show.
So we started to think about our own list.
So we started thinking about our own list.
I'm asking for everyone's thanks.
We started talking about it around this time.
I don't know.
We have a room.
Like a conference room.
We get together there.
We'll play this song, and we'll do this kind of thing.
We talked about how dangerous it is, and that's why we asked you to set it up, but
Before returning it to the board. Oh, I didn't show the video.
I had an erection on my hand.
I put out the video inside.
I've already shown all of them.
But first, I ask the board how they want to make it.
I ask them one by one.
We get it all together.
And then we talk about the song.
We talked about what we're going to do.
I said, "Let's come up with the songs that you want to play.
There were too many songs that we wanted to play.
Well, almost all of them.
Almost all of them.
You know...
That's right.
Almost all of them.
But the theme of this tour is
"coming-of-age novels".
which is the theme of this tour.
So I pulled out the novel
novel, so we pulled down the novel to create a sense of youth, or
A sense of thunder.
Is this tiny?
I don't know...
It's extremely low.
I'm hearing some kind of recibel.
I don't know what to do.
But I can't do it anymore.
I don't know what to do about the recibel
It's pretty low.
Can it go to a fault? This environment is...
Another pretty low level.
Why are the levels so low?
I don't know.
I'm not getting any recvels.
Well, I'm not getting any recibels, so I guess that's OK.
You're taking it easy on me.
I'm the standard.
I understand.
That's good.
Hey. Hey.
Feels good.
So...
Why are you laughing with me?
Even at the beginning.
What's the order of the set disk?
The order of the discs.
"Let's put them in blocks, in the order they appear in the novels.
We talked about putting them in the set disk in the order they appeared in the novels, block by block.
This was just one idea, and it disappeared, but in the end...
Yeah, that's right.
Bill, that was enough.
A little off.
It was the second song at the Fancy.
Maybe it's still daydreaming.
Open?
Maybe we're off from there.
That's right.
That's one of the things that happened.
Yeah, I know.
But it felt like fun.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I was thinking about this...I'm thinking...
I think we're pretty much on the same page.
Oh, right!
That was the important part.
You know what?
That's it!
I can't go home or something,
We're in agreement.
Yes, we did. We did.
We all wanted to do it.
Yeah, we wanted to do it.
If we wanted to, we couldn't leave.
Yeah, that's right.
It's so adolescent.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He calls it adolescence.
And you say it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
How did you decide on the venue?
I was in charge.
What's your favorite song?
Uh-huh.
It's below my mood.
Which one?
Which is it?
The song or the theme?
You want to talk about both?
Yes, sir.
What's up?
No, no, no, no, no.
Well, the song... the future song...
You know, the song that everyone wanted to play.
Mitch? I don't know.
that are out of the classics?
We've got a lot of songs that are off the classics.
We also picked up a lot of songs that we didn't play on the last tour.
that we didn't play on the last tour.
But as much as possible, we try to keep the recent songs
as much as possible.
So, 8:05 was on the schedule last time, but
But on this tour, we're going to play different songs each day.
but on this tour, we played a new song each day.
I think that's when we made the decision.
At that time
It was the left song on November 11th, so
The last song I played was "Boku Yale".
We all agreed on this one.
Well then, here you go.
Yes...
Yes, but we've only done Boku Yale once.
But it feels like a final performance.
That's true.
I thought it would be more emotional if I included my opinion.
So I decided to do it there.
It's just a memory.
Yes.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah.
That's paint, too.
I'm a pretty personal person.
The fact that it's a place where people can see the faults...
I think it's a place where people can see the faults.
That's what I thought.
What did you think?
This is my first time.
I've only done it once.
That's right.
I've only done it twice.
I've only done it once.
Then you can see when there's too many of them.
I didn't want to see it the second time.
Good night.
Souvenir nibbles
Souvenir nibbles.
I'd never heard of them before. They were so good.
There you have it.
They sold Minadore's snacks.
Mm-hmm.
I hope it's okay.
I'm impressed.
I'm glad.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
That's good.
Yes. - Yes.
Okay. Ready.
Like this.
Flat.
And then there was Iwai's decapitation, which was difficult this time.
What we were asking you to look forward to this time was...
There is a line that is read out at the beginning of the concert.
When you open the website, it is the first line that appears.
It was something that had never been done before on this tour.
It's something we haven't done on tour before.
It's something that other teams don't do very often, and it's also something that helped us decide on our own concept.
It was also the point where we decided on our own concept.
We decided to do it because we thought it was something we needed to do.
It's like a school, isn't it?
Yes, in that context.
How did you decide on the location?
It's my birthday, so we decided on a place near Sanjaku.
And in Osaka, the big Osaka.
And the leader will be the last one.
Well, it's kind of nice.
We had so much fun we had to slow it down.
After we took the picture, we got the soundtrack.
Oh, yeah.
There was one time, as I recall. That one.
A lot of people think it's live.
Yes, it's not live.
That's right, it wasn't.
That's why we couldn't help it.
Yes, we couldn't.
We didn't understand.
The final theory was a little bit...
It was amazing. The stories started to overlap.
I'm sorry.
I have to do it again at the end.
Oh, shut up.
The stories keep echoing.
But did you guys hear that? This one.
All the way to the end.
Just a sound.
Did anyone notice?
It was closed at the end.
That's right.
And I ended the story.
Something like that.
Did anyone notice that?
In the last show, you turned the page.
That's right.
There's a lot more to it than you might think.
Oh! I heard that!
You heard me! You heard me!
Oh, yeah!
I like the way the penguins look at me! He said.
Oh, good!
That's what happened.
That's great.
It's closed at the end.
I'm hungry.
I'm down.
Thank you for watching.
Yeah, sure.
LOL.
I didn't finish it, at first.
And I was kind of groping at first.And I was kind of groping my way through it at first.
So I couldn't read it somehow.
And I didn't even know what I was doing.
I wanted to listen to half of it, but I couldn't.
I couldn't listen to the other half, so it was really difficult.
So it was really difficult.
The last corner, you guys were so in sync.
The last corner?
Oh, my God, you're so secretive.
Pile on the layers.
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it was something.
I had the radio, and there was a lot of excitement and laughter.
I thought it was great.
So I'm really grateful for today.
It was a good corner.
That was fun.
It was fun.
From the radio. That's how it developed.
It was fun, everybody had a good time. Radio
Radio is a corner.
Yeah, it's more like...
It's the Vickery Girl's caledio.
Vickery girl.
Yes, please.
Yes, there were some calls during the show, like the one in Sendai.
Mr. Sausaud, please go eat machi chuka at Rinaldi's sometime.
Machichuca.
Oh, yes, we are together!
I want to go to Machichuca.
I have no idea.
I don't even know what machi chuka is!
My dad will make fun of me for the rest of my life.
Talking about Machichucca.
You don't know anything about Machichuca.
I'm always surprised that he doesn't know about Machichuca.
Every time I tell him about Lina and Lulie, he's like, "That's it.
No more?
Yeah, it's all about that.
You know, Lina and Lulie are from Machichuca.
Oh, no, you don't talk like that.
You don't talk to them.
I say it all the time.
We have to go.
Machichuca?
It's like your father's memories are in the people he's been to.
Right, so it's like a stranger is on the person who went there.
Mayu, Shantou Tanchan
Shantou, Dantou-danmyan
Dan-dan-myan
Daibu no, he said, I went to eat this!
Well, but a lot of fans are sending them to me.
There are people who have eaten it and sent it to me through DMs and stuff like that.
I feel like I've eaten everywhere!
Oh, it was me.
I feel like I made it.
It was good, but everyone sent it to me.
I feel like I was able to eat it.
I felt like I could eat it.
I feel like I ate it.
It's so hard!
Thank you for watching.
Good night.
Mr. Minced meat...
Mr. Minced meat.
It's all about mixing things up.
It's all mixed up.
So you're out.
Yes, I did.
It's all mixed up.
This outfit is...
You know...
It's from our manager.
From Hikiku, right?
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
This is the kind of costume we really want to make.
That's what I wanted to make.
It's the costume I've always wanted to make.
Yes...
I don't know...
something
What is it?
A dream?
Is that what this is about?
Shall we read it?
Oh, yeah, that's it!
You can say that!
Like the princess of Serio.
Like the princess of Celio.
"I've always wanted to make a costume designed like the princess of Serio.
This costume is the result of that wish!
It's very princess-like.
The skirt is very heavy.
And the skirt inside is actually...
It's like a honeycomb or something.
The wires are a little bit...
It's like a support for a garden.
Garden garden?
Like in a garden garden?
The kind of posts that go into the skirt.
That's why you can see the skirt more beautifully. It's round.
That's how it's done.
The shoes are different from the ones I usually wear.
Shoes that are a little rounder than the ones I usually wear.
The color has also changed.
Red.
Costume
So I'm very particular about that.
And the ribbons on the outside of the shoes.
It's cute.
Cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
What do you think?
It's very expensive.
It's adorable.
It's cute.
It's a skirt with a luxurious curtain look. It's beautiful.
She's very pretty.
Wasn't she wearing a skirt at the Sasuka show?
She wasn't wearing a skirt.
It was amazing. When the skirt turned, it spread out so much.
It was so beautiful.
And it's like a double layer.
The skirt was on the front.
If there was a skirt, it would overlap the skirt on the outside.
It's so beautiful and cute!
Ladies and gentlemen, there were short-sleeved and long-sleeved versions of this dress.
Actually, yes, there were.
Which do you prefer?
Short-sleeved or long-sleeved?
Short-sleeved for me.
I'm long-sleeved.
This one is long-sleeved.
It's hot
It stings my road book when I'm walking.
Ah!
I'm Japanese
I got caught in this bathtub and my mouth got cold
My microphone got stuck in the bathtub.Mike got stuck with a gun.
My mouth went cold, cold-blooded.
Because Japanese.
Oh, here's a big breath.
I got a little ticked off.
Oh, I see.
I'm, you know, a rehearsal leaser.
Um, what was that?
I'm singing... There's no ah...
He's not here.
I'm a fan of something.
He ran away...
I don't know...
I'm gonna run away.
Oh, my God!
I fell on my half-file.
It hurts so bad.
I'm so embarrassed, Gan-chan.
I'm in shit trouble.
Oh, well...
At best, I fell down, half a dozen times.
I don't know how many other times I've fallen.
Fucking trouble, you know?
Once.
Last day.
It was the last day.
It was the last day, and I fell down on the first parlé.
I realized that I might have fallen.
And then I realized I was kind of squatting.
I was just kind of squatting.
I don't even remember why I fell.
Really? Yeah, I think I might have.
What happened to Killalips and the first chorus?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're not? I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm lost a lot.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
No, you're just so generous.
I don't know... the first chorus and the second chorus...
The first chorus and the second chorus are in slightly different positions in my mind.
And I was like, "Oh my God, which is it?
I said, "It's neither.
Neither?
I said it in the position where it's neither, and I thought, "I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
There's a blank space.
I was in a big hurry.
I couldn't rehearse the investment in there.
I felt like I did it while thinking about it in my head
The last bite!
Thank you for the food!
If you liked this video, please like, subscribe to the channel, and comment!
See you in the next video!
Bye!
Thanks for watching!
I'm not really trying to go against the grain here.
I'm on the team with the long hair.
I'm going to wear a ponytail today.
I like twin-tails today.
What are you doing in Osaka? Do you want to go to Nagano?
I don't know.
I'm just saying.
Not really.
Your hair...
If it's too long...
What do you mean?
If you have long hair...
Not much.
Not much
Too much.
It covers your hair.
I think it's hard to do that.
But five times.
Yeah, not too much.
Yes, not so much.
You're right.
I went to Osaka and Tokyo France
And also
Nagoya, not Scope.
What did I do?
This is Nagoya.
Oh...
Mini and...
And Kimin, the Bobsman.
This is Mini-chan.
And Mini-chan.
And Neytale.
Sixth one.
I was working on the third one.
But you know what?
You know, the ones with their foreheads sticking out, it's a deformation.
I'm amazed at how many of you have your foreheads out.
I think I've been there.
At 8:05 in Nagoya.
The one in front of Moa-chan.
Like this.
Oh, I've seen them before at the Satsukai.
That's right.
How did you know?
We all knew.
Why don't we put roses on it?
Oh, roses.
Yes, roses.
I was wondering if I should put a rose on it or not.
I'd like to see us all put out a cat sometime.
I'm sorry we have to do it together.
Was it hard? A little.
If you come to my house...
I'll stop you.
Thank you for watching today.
Look for a new video in the next issue!
Thank you for watching.
Delicious.
You have a face that looks like it's blowing in the wind.
Much.
You have that look on your face.
It's delicious!
I had a face like that.
I wanted to eat it.
That's what they were saying.
They were saying that.
Backstage happenings?
Backstage? Backstage?
That's important.
I've been hit.
Kon-takarin.
Who ate my bento?
I don't think so.
But it's a real mystery.
No, Takashi definitely ate it.
I'm sure it's C's fault.
C?
It's Kachi's fault.
Why am I the only one?
It was there.
It's nothing.
I can tell just by looking at it.
I'll hold on to it.
I know.
Why not?
What else?
We're out of hoodies.
Yeah, I know.That's right.
What's this?
What is it?
I threw it out.
I didn't throw it out.
Not that I'm aware of.
You know, the hoodie from the last edition.
Parker had a name on it.
It has a face on it.
It has a name on it.
In Aichi's case...
Mo-chan's hoodie is missing.
Even if I brought it back.
I didn't bring it home.
Digging for a leg?
I brought back a leg. We were able to exchange it.
That's where he came.
And then we realized we didn't have Ma-chan's hoodie.
We were exchanging costumes.
So I looked for a place that exchanges costumes.
She said she couldn't find her hoodie in one of them.
So I went to the place where they exchange costumes, and I couldn't find a single hoodie, and I said, "I can't find one.
But his name is up there, too.
He said it's too big and he's not likely to hide it.
He's not going to throw it anywhere.
He wouldn't bring it home?
I really don't.
But the clothes are on the floor.
I'm looking in Kellin's.
No, it's not.
I don't know.
It's this way.
I saw it.
That's good.
I like it.
There you go.
He went to hide it.
I lost something this time.
Yeah.
It's a little difficult when you think of it that way.
I don't know,
Your brother.
Droke.
I'm scared.
I'm scared, I'm getting scared now.
Hmmm.
I think there was something.
Oh, not here.
In front of Taichi's location.
Oh.
There was no mirror.
Oh, oh, oh.
Put your forehead out.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Now...
I don't have a lot of mirrors in my room.
You don't have a lot of mirrors.
I had a little bit of a mirror.
But for some reason, it's fixed in place, and if I don't move it...
I had to move it.
And there was a seat for the members of the group.
But we couldn't move it to that position.
We had to move ourselves.
We were all looking in the mirror on about three different levels.
We were all looking in the mirror.
The second level was also with three brothers.
I'd iron at the bottom, beak in the middle, and do hair at the top.
There's a lot of lines, even pretty much, all the time.
That's for sure.
We don't have any mirrors.
Sell them in the dressing room.
Is that what you do with your accutane?
Yes, they do.
They're on sale.
The last one.
Reara.
With Leala on it.
Rare, isn't it?
I'm sure they all got them at Penzey's.
Not there.
They don't wear it.
Why isn't everyone wearing it?
They're not on.
Only three of us are wearing them.
What are you talking about?
It didn't go over your head.
It's a little hard to shape.
The bangs are a little harder to get right.
There are so many ways to do it.
Did you sell out of the Axta?
Sold out.
Did you resell it?
You can't say you're going to keep it now, can you?
I don't know.
Good.
But everyone...
You bought a lot.
Thank you very much.
So I guess that's how the spring tour is going to be.
But the dance teacher praised us a lot.
And the letter teacher gave me a lot of compliments yesterday, so...
I'm glad we were able to bury it in a good way.
Thank you very much for the spring tour!
Thank you very much.
So, we performed a new song, Hell Wing, as an encore at Shinagawa Park on the spring tour.
But it will be available for pre-sale on the 17th, so have you heard it?
Have you heard it?
What do you think? What do you think?
Is there anything you like about it?
Certainly.
I like the lyrics here.
Hellwing, I like it better.
Good, I'm listening to it.
refreshing
beautiful
It's true.
I'm listening to it a lot.
I like the lyrics.
The choreography is cute.
She memorized it.
That's great.
But, go on, go home.
I want you to do the choreography for the heels, too.
I remember.
Listen to me.
Fly it down the hall.
I'm listening.
You care about this?
Yes, I do.
It's hard, isn't it?
Oh, it's a little hard.
Oh, it's spilling all over the place.
It's not coming in.
But it was a little difficult this time.
Dancing, right?
Yeah, it was difficult.
There was a lot of moving around.
Yes.
But the dancing was really cool.
Yeah, it's cool.
You should see it.
His neck is so cool!
Yeah, the neck. I just love it here.
Necks are so cool!
Mr. River, I love the "go, go, go, go, go, go" part.
But it's right there.But it's over there.
Nyaroo, that's what it's all about.
Tail window is a spring theme to cheer up new life
sharp train
illustration
Supporting new life in spring
Rina's stingray is amazing!
A ray?
It's not a new day.
It's a ray.
I'm moving up in the rankings.
I'm ranking because I'm ranking up.
The sound.
This is... it's hard to sing, isn't it?
The song seems easy to sing.
But it's surprisingly difficult.
The part where the decision is made by the song is difficult.
The rapid succession is difficult.
I can't get the swing.
It's difficult, but...
The A melody is sometimes low
Singing this point ahead together
I think it's very refreshing and a wonderful place to be born
The new song, Tailwind, will also be included!
The first single for the major label will be released on June 21!
Yes, so, in advance of the release, I would like to say
I'd like to commemorate the release of the song, and I'll be releasing it on the website.
It's coming out next week!
That's early!
We're going to start!
Early!
Soon!
It's almost here.
Surprisingly.
Because this weekend, more and more anime events will be held.
And then next week, the releases will start.
One of them is Maruimen no Okudo in Shinjuku on Saturday, April 29th!
Yes, sir.
You said it's been a long time since you two met, right?
That's right.
It's the first time.
It's a pretty nice venue.
You might want to bring some of the tsukimi, tsukimi was made for you.
You might want to have a tsukimi made.
You might want to have a tsukimi, tsukimi made
I try not to forget.
Yes, sir.
What?
It's been cut to pieces.
Come with me.
What? What do you mean?
It's something Gongbong does.
It's bad, isn't it?
I can't find my legs.
I'm sorry.
So, Molly Week has started.
The next day is a distribution event.
Molly Week is at the Kawase.
Oh!
You're going so much, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Since there are certain events during the two years and so on,
Many of us might see each other for 4 days in a row.
That's right.
We see each other every day.
Almost like members.
Almost members.
And until about the 25th of June, most of the members have already gathered,
I hope you will come and visit us at the Ladies' Event.
I hope you will come and visit us at the Ladies' Event. Thank you very much.
Well, I guess I'll start with the announcement.
We have to do it in time.
Yes. Here, everyone, we have a new announcement.
We have a new announcement.
Announcement?
I have three new announcements.
Three new announcements!
They're great.
Please.
Okay, here's the first one.
I'm going to write it down on this piece of paper and we're going to hug on each of the three shots.
Okay. You want me to hide it for the third one?
The first one.
Oh, really?
Okay, let's go to the very middle.
You want me to hide it?
Sure, sure.
The last one's wrong.
I'm a stickler.
Okay, let's see if we can get everyone's...
LOL!
(laughter)
Not enough, not enough
You're all in the mood for...
Are you okay?
Now I would like to make an announcement.
Yes.
We, Lucca..,
We've decided to go with Monmonland.
Yay!
First of all.
Saturday, the 30th of September,
Yes.
Venue,
Shibuya Peets!
Yay!
Peets is Aimi, right?
Don't let them see what's underneath.
Yes, I'm Aimi.
This is Shibuya, September 30, at Shibuya Beats,
This is the first time for me to visit this venue,
The venue is a recently built barque, and it is very beautiful,
I hope you will all come and visit us in Shibuya.
Please come and visit us in Shibuya.
The second one is on October 14. This is also a one-man live concert.
The place is Tokyo Girno Club.
I love Giruno Club.
I have never performed at Giruno Club by myself,
I have done Taipan live before.
We have done it before, but we, Ligia, have done it at a different time or something,
We didn't do that. Birthday.
Birthday. Birthday about the third grade.
It's like us. Birthdays are close to each other and so on,
We hope you will come and visit us at the Kiminoma Club in October.
And the third one, it's also a man-man show.
This is amazing. This is great.
When?
This one is a man-man show on January 21, 2024.
Next year!
We're coming up to the 20-year mark.
I'll announce the venue.
Yes.
Ebisu Liquid Rum!
Congratulations!
Today, we have announced three one-man shows,
We have already scheduled them until next January.
Please keep your schedules open until next January at the Liquid Room,
We hope that you will be able to join us,
Our goal for the spring tour was to sell out all the venues,
Unfortunately, we were only able to sell out the Osaka show this spring tour.
Unfortunately, only the Osaka show was sold out this spring tour, so we decided to make up for it,
We are now working toward the goal of selling out all of the shows,
We are aiming to sell out all the tickets for all three one-man shows.
We will do our best to sell out all the tickets for the three one-man shows announced this time,
We would like to ask for your cooperation,
We hope that you will participate in as many one-man shows as possible.
We will announce the details of the live concerts at a later date, so please come and join us with your friends and family. Please come and visit us with your friends and family.
Yes, that's right. What do you think of these three one-man shows you have announced?
I am looking forward to them. There are a lot of things to look forward to.Fun. It's packed, lots of it.
I'd like to see you put it on the schedule.
Of course.
I hope you've already said all you're going to say and used it.
Absolutely.
It's called September 30th.
Don't say it.
July and August.
After a lot of summer festivals and stuff.
It's after a lot of summer festivals.
So I hope that people who like us at those festivals will come to our shows.
Okinawa Club is different from a regular house.
What do you call it?
It's a different name.
Hut?
Hut is a little different.
I'll say it all out loud.
It's a different kind of place. It's a steading, it's a stage, it's a...
I don't know what it's going to be like.
I'm really looking forward to seeing what kind of show it's going to be.
I'm looking forward to working hard in this generation and making a fun festival with you all on January 21 at the Liquid Room, our sacred place in Ebisu, right?
Yes, that's right. We will do our best to sell out the venue, and I am sure that the contents of the concert, which will probably be decided in the future, will be wonderful.
I hope you are looking forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
That's great. I'm glad you have so many plans.
We have a single coming out in June, a med's event, and a summer ice cream party,
Dragon Girl is coming.
Yes, I'll see you every day.
I'll be able to see you every day. Almost every day.
You are happy, aren't you?
Almost.
Yes. So, I guess that's the end for today.
Yes.
Okay. Next up, we have "Idol Generation" on the 22nd, "Coro Face" on the 23rd, and "Shinjuku Maneimen" next week on the 29th.
And next week on the 29th, we will see you at Shinjuku Manemen, so please look forward to it.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. That's all for now,
This is REVUE.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.